<resources>
    <string name="app_name">M-Search</string>
    <string name="country_selection_title">Country Selection</string>
    <string name="mode_selection_title">Mode selection</string>
    <string name="manual_enter_title">Manual identification</string>
    <string name="app_next">Next</string>
    <string name="app_back">Back</string>
    <string name="return_back">Return</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="test_med">Heroin</string>
    <string name="transparency_statement">Transparency Statement</string>
    <string name="original_med">Original Medicine</string>
    <string name="results">Results</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="transparency_content">The M-Search team utilizes an international database matching system that ranks medicine matches in terms of closeness to the original medicine and in accordance to medication matching guidelines. We utilize these databases specifically to match on active ingredients and rank further based on intake method and dosage amounts. This helps the team ensure the best results of equivalency at the top of our program to help you quickly find what you are looking for.</string>
    <string name="select_from">Select country from:</string>
    <string name="select_to">Select country to:</string>
    <string name="mode_manual">Manual</string>
    <string name="mode_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="need_help">Need help?</string>
    <string name="result_explanation">The results are labeled by their brand name and are sorted by relevancy. In order to obtain more information about each result tap the respective item</string>
    <string name="ndc_explanation">The ndc number on the packaging might contain 3 numbers. Please only include the first 2. For example if the packaging says 0069–1085–30 please only include 0069–1085</string>
    <string name="loading_failed">Loading failed</string>
    <string name="app_description">The easy way to identify medicinal alternatives!</string>
    <string name="mode_selection_instructions">Please select which mode you want to use to identify your medication</string>
    <string name="manual_instructions">Please enter the 2 numbers of the ndc code as indicated on the packaging separated by the hyphen</string>
    <string name="country_selection_instructions">Please select the initial country the medication is coming from and the country you want to search for alternatives in.</string>
</resources>